The SCOAN Sunday Service
Ma beremole ma gbega
I will bow and praise His name
Ma jijo Jesu daadaa daadaa daa
I will dance for Jesus with vigor
Gbe soke
Let’s lift Him higher
Ma beremole ma gbega
I will bow and praise His name
Ma jijo Jesu daadaa daadaa daa
I will dance for Jesus with vigor
Gbe soke
Let’s lift Him higher
Somebody scream!
The SCOAN Sunday Service
Somebody shout!
Jump, jump, jump...
The SCOAN Sunday Service
One, two, three, four...
Otun gbe mi soke
He has lifted me up
Loke loke loke
Higher higher higher
Otun gbe mi soke
He has lifted me up
Loke loke loke
Higher higher higher
Otun gbe mi soke
He has lifted me up
Loke loke loke
Higher higher higher
Otun gbe mi soke
He has lifted me up
Loke loke loke
Higher higher higher
Everybody gbe soke
Everybody lift Him higher
Ma beremole ma gbega
I will bow and praise His name
Ma jijo Jesu daadaa daadaa daa
I will dance for Jesus with vigor
Gbe soke
Let’s lift Him higher
Glory be to the Lord in the highest
Hallelujah
The SCOAN Sunday Service
Good Morning, Church!
Good Morning.
The SCOAN Sunday Service
I was looking at what you were seeing; the joy is so overwhelming.
I know some people here don't know how to dance, but the way they were dancing;
I was, "Oh, my God!"
The SCOAN Sunday Service
The Spirit of God can inspire one to begin to...
Are you seeing that mood?
Yes!
Please, help me; hold it...
Thank you.
You may be seated.
The free spirit to fellowship – I think this is what is happening now.
The free spirit to fellowship – spirit that has nothing against his neighbour,
nothing against anyone.
Your situation, you leave it for God; don’t worry yourself.
You just see yourself the way you were created.
You are what God says you are.
You have what God says you have.
You can do what God says you can do.
That is a free spirit.
Viewers all over the world, I know you are with us and we are with you.
Bless you!
Like I have said, you need a free spirit.
Jesus cannot share with a heart that is full of unforgiveness.
- Are you with me?
- Yes.
He cannot share with a heart that is full of bitterness, envy, jealousy.
The Holy Spirit cannot share with such a heart so you need a free spirit.
It is this free spirit that craves for the Word of God, for Jesus Himself.
To hearts that are holding offence – be free, in the name of Jesus!
Amen!
To hearts that are full of unforgiveness – check your heart.
To hearts that are full of unforgiveness, bitterness, hatred,
envy, jealousy, still holding the pain of the past -
be free, in the name of Jesus!
Amen!
Do you know I am talking to your heart?
Yes.
No no no, you don't know.
Do you know I am talking to your heart?
Let your heart answer me.
Yes.
I say, “Be free, in the name of Jesus!”
Amen!
To hearts that are full of unforgiveness, bitterness, hatred, jealousy, envy, anger -
be free, in the name of Jesus Christ!
Amen!
Viewers all over the world, check yourselves.
If you are still holding grudges against anyone, you have already offended the Holy Spirit.
Holding grudges, bitterness, envy, jealousy, against anyone -
you have already grieved the Holy Spirit.
Be free, in the name of Jesus!
Amen!
Because we would not be able to move forward;
I would not be able to carry you along – hearts that are full of offence, full of envy, jealousy.
You would just be seeing what is happening but to be part of what is happening is impossible
because of offence, because of envy,
because of jealousy, because of bitterness.
Check your heart.
Say, “My heart, be free!
My heart, crave for God; crave for the Word of God!"
I cannot hear you.
My heart, be free!
My heart!
Our heart is the contact point, the place of point for Jesus.
If Jesus is coming to you, it is not your eyes, it is not your mouth, it is not your appearance -
it is your heart.
My heart, crave for the Word of God!
My heart, yearn for the Word of God!
Overflow Congregation
Sometimes we can be dancing, be happy, just emotional - feeling.
Happiness can be found around, just in what is happening.
Just get it around, and after leaving that place it is over.
My heart!
I want to carry you along; this is why we are talking to your real self – your heart.
- Hallelujah!
- Amen.
Be free, in the name of Jesus!
Amen!
Are you there with me?
I am not saying this body.
I know you are on the seat; I know you are looking at me.
You can be looking at me, sitting down, whereas you are not here.
The SCOAN Sunday Service
Inner my heart
Lord I want to be like Jesus
Overflow Congregation
If your heart is not at its best, don’t be surprised if the Bible is no more real to you -
the Bible you carry is no more real, is a literature, is history.
If your heart is not at its best, the Bible you carry becomes a history book, not Bible.
Tell your neighbour, “If my heart is not at its best, the Bible you carry automatically becomes history,
a history book just about apostles, stories about apostles, just history, literature.
It is no longer Bible if your heart is not at its best.
That is why we have not been seeing the reflection of the Bible in your life.
People see you carrying the Bible -
no, it is literature, a mere history book you are carrying because your heart is not at its best.
Your heart must be at its best.
Sometimes, if your heart is not at its best, you can even drop it and talk to yourself -
get yourself together.
If my heart is not at its best, I would not come here; I would not be here.
I would not have contact with the Holy Spirit.
It is when our heart is at its best, there is contact.
Inner my heart
Lord I want to be like Jesus
These are the things you need to do before prayer.
Are you at your best before prayer, before, “In Jesus’ name”?
Your heart must be at its best before you begin to pray.
You don’t just stand up and say, “Let us pray”.
As you are watching the virtues, the healing power,
take this song, continue to sing this song:
Inner my heart
Lord I want to be like Jesus
Each time you see that healing happen, it is the presence of God -
through His Word, by His Spirit.
“Jesus” – you see people getting healed; it means Jesus is there.
Quickly invite Him to your heart; let Him take more of you.
You have been praying; now, you are seeing it coming.
You can see, "That is Jesus."
Quickly invite Him to your heart; get Him in your heart.
- Hallelujah!
- Amen.
TT ROBERT BEGIER 29/06/2018